Kenenna Anyaegbunam

Product Designer

Email: akenenna@gmail.com Linkedin: @kene-anyaegbunam

I'm a Product Designer with over four (4) years of experience crafting digital products and experiences. I have built expertise in the Fintech space, and also had the privilege of working with great teams in the creator economy, e-commerce, Artificial Intelligence, and most recently, AR/VR.

Experience

Tradevu Head Of Product

Jul 2024 - Present

Full-Time, Remote, London

- Leading 6-person product & engineering team building Tradevu's enterprise platform
- Drive product vision for Tradevu Flex comprehensive suite for managing purchase orders, shipments, and invoices
- Achieved 78% user satisfaction rating (5/5) through usercentric product development methodology

African Technopreneurs | Product Designer

Nov 2023 - Present

Contract, Remote, South Africa

- Designed and developed content for websites like EARN,
 AYWB, African Techno, and It's Time for Africa.
- Optimized UX for the Shopify-based 180by2 site, improving user flow and functionality.

Pivo Africa

Full-Time, Remote, Lagos

• Design Lead | Mar 2022 - Nov 2023

Managed the design team and drove strategy across branding and product initiatives.

- Brand & Product Designer Oct 2021 Mar 2022
 - Built Pivo's brand identity and product designs from the ground up, ensuring consistency and market alignment.

Color Me | Brand & Product Designer

Jan 2020 - Oct 2021

Full-Time, Remote, Lagos

- Designed and developed Color Me's internal brand, website, and graphics, ensuring a cohesive visual identity.
- Created brand and product designs for various clients, delivering tailored solutions that aligned with their needs.

Education

Interaction Design Foundation

Aug 2023 | Product Adoption & Appropriation

Google (Udacity)

Aug 2021 | Product Design

Georgia Institute Of Technology

Nov 2019 | User Interface And Experience Design

University Of Lagos

Dec 2016 | B.Sc. Biochemistry

Skills

Design Leadership
Design Optimisation
Scaled Agile Framework
User Research
AR/VR Design
Responsive Web Design
Mobile Application Design
Brand Design

Tools

Figma
Adobe Illustrator
Adobe Photoshop
Adobe After Effects
Rive